<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shing Tak Lam</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shing Tak Lam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>2020 Shing Tak Lam. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rosetta</title>
      <link>/posts/rosetta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rosetta/</guid>
      <description>From personal experience, when learning an interactive theorem prover like Lean, there&#39;s a lot of &amp;quot;this should be obvious, now how do I do this&amp;quot; when getting started. Part of this is the rigour involved, as some things which may seem obvious are actually more subtle than it initially seems. In other cases, it may be that the approach taken by the mathematics library is different to the one used commonly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Formalising polynomials</title>
      <link>/posts/formalising_polynomials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/formalising_polynomials/</guid>
      <description>One thing that comes up frequently in mathematics is the idea of polynomials, and we would like to be able to reason on any polynomial. To do this requires us to develop the theory of polynomials.
To start off, we need the definition of polynomials. Wikipedia says
 In mathematics, a polynomial is an expression consisting of variables (also called indeterminates) and coefficients, that involves only the operations of addition, subtraction, multiplication, and non-negative integer exponents of variables</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Shing. I am a first year undergraduate at the University of Cambridge, reading Mathematics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page has a partial list of the projects that I have worked on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>